布兰特  档案上写着
So, Brent, I see from your file
你生前做材料生意
you were in the materials business.
对  范围很广
Yeah, big time.
绳啊  弦啊  乙烯基塑料  合成纤维  橡胶
Strings, chords, vinyl, synthetics, rubber--
现在做硫化品了  大生意
we do vulcanized now, so that's huge.
还有金属  铝材  黄铜  铜制品  还有什么
Plus metals-- aluminum, brass, copper... what else...
-钢铁  -不做钢铁生意
- Steel? - No, not steel.
没出息才会做钢铁生意
Steel's a sucker's game.
聚合物  涂料  内件
Polymers, coatings, internals--
打开一个暖通空调
you crack open an HVAC?
材料都是我们生产的范围
That is all us.
这里有高尔夫球场吗  最好有
Is there golf here? There freaking better be.
你自己逛一逛  我就不打扰你了
Okay, well, why don't you explore around a bit while I go far away
如果有什么需要  就找珍妮特
and if you need anything, you can always ask Janet.